

# Parvindra Tongar (UI/UX Designer)

UX Designer | Startups | Figma, Sketch | Prototypes, Wireframes, User-flow | HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap | Responsive Web Design

# **CONTACT**

Mobile: +91-7428098010 Email: parvtongar@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

### Post Graduation (2009)

Aptech ACCP(Web Design and Development)

#### **Graduation (2007)**

Bachelor of Arts (CCS University)

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

User Experience Designer with **10+ years** of experience in interaction design working with startups. Follow a quick approach to design and go live within a short period of time.

I have experience in Web Application, Admin Panels and Mobile-based designs from paper sketch to interconnect screens prototypes.

#### **PROJECTS**

# **CurrencyEx, 12 Weeks**

An application that allowed for business-to-business foreign currency and same-currency payments

#### MovTek, 24 Weeks

MovTek provides Air and Sea Freight services across the globe.

## **Hire Military Jobs, 24 Weeks**

This project helps Retired Military persons to find jobs in corporate.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Apr 2016 to Present

#### Lead Designer at Nuage Biztech pvt Itd

I have worked on multi-domain Web and Mobile Apps. have versatile experience in Designing Admin Panels, Web Apps and Websites.

May 2013 to Oct 2015

## **Website Designer at Rati software solutions**

Website Designer, Responsive Design, Web Designer, HTML Coder, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.

Aug 2008 to May 2013

## **Website Designer at ekant solutions**

Website Designer, Web Designer, HTML5, CSS3, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.